卡爾有一個不尋常的要求。
Carl had an unusual request.
他希望自己的骨灰撒到北方。
He wanted his ashes to be scattered up north.
你死定了。
You're dead.
你好？
Hello?
外面有人嗎？
Anyone out there?
是緊急狀況。
It's an emergency.
有個小孩在打瞌睡。
There's been a kid napping.
有人嗎？
Anyone?
你好？
Hello?
哦！
Oh!
嘿！
Hey there!
你在這兒做什麼？
What are you doing up here?
這只是一點點釣魚而已。
It's just a little fishin'.
自己一個人嗎？
By yourself?
是的。
Yeah.
你看，你不會碰巧知道希爾達湖在哪裡吧？
See, you wouldn't happen to know where a lake hildar is, would you?
是的。
Yeah.
剛回到這裡的山坡上。
Just back over the hill here.
好的。
Okay.
嗯，保持溫暖。
Well, stay warm.
她想要什麼？
What did she want?
我給她指明了去湖邊的方向。
I gave her directions to the lake.
親愛的，你不再對人那麼好了嗎？
Honey, do you stop doing so nice to people?
你可以。
You could.
我不會離開你。
I'm not leaving you.
我們要做什麼？
What are we gonna do?
我們繼續前進。
We keep going.
就這麼簡單。
Simple as that.
哦！
Oh!
我們必須讓這項工作成功！
We have to make this work!
你這是做什麼？
What are you doing this?
哦！
Oh!